=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 20=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 20 =
How dare you Xia Family!
كيف تجرؤ على عائلة شيا!
Tried to deceive me?
حاولت أن تخدعني؟
Uncle Gu,
العم جو
my father was trying to save face for two families.
كان والدي يحاول حفظ ماء الوجه لأسرتين.
This was the last plan we had.
كانت هذه آخر خطة لدينا.
I did that out of despair.
فعلت ذلك بدافع اليأس.
You were trying to save the support from us Gu's!
كنت تحاول حفظ الدعم منا غو!
Sorry, uncle Gu.
آسف يا عمي جو.
I suppose the Xia Family
أفترض عائلة شيا
has nothing to help.
ليس لديه ما يساعد.
Dad.
أب.
Why didn't you give me a heads-up?
لماذا لم تعطيني تنبيه؟
Your wife was replaced.
تم استبدال زوجتك.
What's there to negotiate?
ماذا هناك للتفاوض؟
You found out.
اكتشفت.
Looks like you found out earlier
يبدو أنك اكتشفت في وقت سابق
that she's a counterfeit.
أنها مزيفة.
It's not what you think it is.
ليس الأمر كما تعتقد.
We...
نحن...
I'm giving you three days
سأعطيك ثلاثة أيام
to clear up this mess.
لتوضيح هذه الفوضى.
Send this girl back to wherever she should've been.
أرسل هذه الفتاة إلى حيث كان يجب أن تكون.
Our Gu Family won't tolerate her!
عائلة Gu لن تتسامح معها!
No. She's still helpful to me.
لا. إنها لا تزال تساعدني.
Are you fine?
هل أنت بخير؟
Stop here, please.
قف هنا من فضلك.
Yo go home first.
اذهب للمنزل أولا.
I'm going to the hospital to see my dad.
أنا ذاهب إلى المستشفى لرؤية والدي.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
Don't bother.
لا تهتم.
Help! Help!
مساعدة!  مساعدة!
I suppose you Xia Family has nothing to help!
أفترض أن عائلة شيا ليس لديها شيء للمساعدة!
Xia Qiange can help the Gu's
يمكن لـ Xia Qiange مساعدة Gu's
win the first place at the national runway.
الفوز بالمركز الأول على المدرج الوطني.
Our market value will surge.
سوف ترتفع قيمتنا السوقية.
You're sure you're not helping out this woman?
هل أنت متأكد أنك لا تساعد هذه المرأة؟
We're together only because of interests.
نحن معًا فقط بسبب المصالح.
You're up.
أنت جاهز.
What happened to me?
ماذا حدث لي؟
Doctor said you were extremely startled.
قال الطبيب إنك كنت مذهولاً للغاية.
But you're fine.
لكنك بخير.
You'll recover with some rest.
سوف تتعافى مع بعض الراحة.
Where's Gu Chengze?
أين قو تشينجزي؟
You're still thinking about him?
هل مازلت تفكر فيه؟
I can summon him for you.
يمكنني استدعائه لك.
Can't you be serious?
ألا يمكنك أن تكون جادا؟
Hey.
يا.
Circle, oval, rectangle,
دائرة ، بيضاوية ، مستطيل ،
there's nothing about me that's square.
لا يوجد شيء عني هذا مربع.
Do you agree that,
هل توافق على ذلك،
if Gu Chengze was half thoughtful as I am,
إذا كان Gu Chengze نصف مدروس مثلي ،
I'd not take a lot of trouble.
لن أتحمل الكثير من المتاعب.
Alright. Whatever you say.
على ما يرام.  أيا كان ما تقوله.
Who are you guys?
من هم يا رفاق؟
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Abduct me in broad daylight?
اختطفني في وضح النهار؟
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
if the Gu's is not sued and broke, I'll...
إذا لم يتم رفع دعوى ضد Gu's وكسرها ، فسوف ...
Answer my questions one by one.
أجب على أسئلتي واحدا تلو الآخر.
Let go!
اتركه!
What is the relationship between you and Xia Qiange?
ما هي العلاقة بينك وبين Xia Qiange؟
Look at you being so mindful of her.
انظر إلى كونك منتبهًا جدًا لها.
And you're afraid to express?
وأنت خائف من التعبير؟
What? Does Mr. Gu get cold feet?
ماذا؟  هل يشعر السيد جو ببرودة القدمين؟
Not up to you to ask.
ليس لك أن تسأل.
Are you really having a grudge
هل حقا لديك ضغينة
because she's Xia Qiange?
لأنها شيا تشيانج؟
Wait, I might have a chance on her.
انتظر ، قد تكون لدي فرصة لها.
Dare you.
اتحداك.
Well, enough of joking.
حسنًا ، يكفي المزاح.
However,
لكن،
I wish you meant you said that day.
أتمنى أن تقصد أنك قلت ذلك اليوم.
Once I
مرة واحدة
did not believe in love at first sight.
لم يؤمن بالحب من النظرة الأولى.
But when I met this girl
لكن عندما قابلت هذه الفتاة
who's outgoing, confident and kind-hearted.
من المنتهية ولايته ، واثق وطيب القلب.
And I fell deeply for her.
وقد وقعت في غرامها بعمق.
The girl that you fell for on runway,
الفتاة التي وقعت في حبها على المدرج ،
was not Xia Qianxun.
لم يكن Xia Qianxun.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟